<<<<<<< HEAD

const questions=[
    {
        "id": 1, 
        "question": "3, 1, 4, 1, 5",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 2, 
        "question": "1, 1, 2, 3, 5",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 3, 
        "question": "1, 4, 9, 16, 25",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "id": 4, 
        "question": "2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "1, 2, 4, 8, 16",
        "answer": 32
    },
];

=======

const questions=[
    {
        "id": 1, 
        "question": "3, 1, 4, 1, 5",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 2, 
        "question": "1, 1, 2, 3, 5",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 3, 
        "question": "1, 4, 9, 16, 25",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "id": 4, 
        "question": "2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "1, 2, 4, 8, 16",
        "answer": 32
    },
];

>>>>>>> c8fcdee71ba7c66544caa5140194e5e6ef829de0
module.exports = questions;